Nice!
You always stand by first with just Mr. Kojima.
Yes, sir.
So it's already started.
That's how it's always done.
I thought for sure you would.
Thank you.
I thought for sure it had already started.
It hasn't started yet, though.
I was over there practicing my vocals.
I'm just looking and talking right now.
I couldn't hear you at all.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I was doing the "American Idol" thing.
I wish I could have heard them do it.
Oh, man, I gotta do Stacomi.
Who's that?
Next.
Yuzu.
But the news is only 19 7 percent.
Shall we do it?
Shall we? What do you say?
No, I'm gonna do this one.
It's gonna be a series.
Maybe it's true.
What if it runs out?
I'm sure.
Really? A flame?
I haven't done flames in a long time.
But that's okay.
Yeah, the flame's doing it.
No.
I've only got 17 yuzu pars.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, I see. So your cell phone wasn't working last week.
That's why.
What do you want me to do?
When you're done with the hauling, then.
Okay.
Get dressed.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, here you go.
Three, two, one.
Are you free later tonight?
Would you go out with me?
I've always wanted to talk to Yume.
Even after the rain stopped, the party was still going on.
Seino!
Let's have a candy flash chat while it's raining!
Ame-shabe for short!
Good evening to all of you who are watching our official YouTube Live Ameflash channel.
We are Ameflash.
I'm in charge of the name calling for the title call this time.
My name is Yume.
I haven't watched it for a while because I've been busy lately, but the buzz was so good that I watched it for the first time in a while.
I was relieved to see that you haven't changed at all.
The coffee song is really good too. He posted that I have to go to the show again.
Thank you very much.
Then next time, don't leave me again.
Yume-chan has to keep it attached.
Please come again.
I wanted to talk to you roundly about this title call by name with me.
I will call one of the people who tweeted their impressions of Ameshabe.
Please tweet your impressions with the hashtag "Ameshabe". Thank you very much.
I'm off to read Spacha right away.
Yaekage, please enjoy Fanta Lemon Premium that was released today.
Thank you very much.
I see.
What? Fanta?
Lemon Premium.
A premium case of Fanta.
Two of them. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next, Nao-san and Ayakane, thank you for your hard work. Everyone was cute and the dancing was great.
Thank you very much.
Koushiro, thank you very much for the Ayakane award and the 2nd place. Hana-chan was cool. I saw many tweets.
Next, Mr. Tui, congratulations on your music video getting over 100,000 views. Ayakane also had a great time. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Next, YTXZ Shippo's feeling, the coffee is really good. I am healed by listening to it repeatedly.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
Now, then.
Ira.
Ira?
Due to a scheduling conflict.
Schedule conflict.
What is it?
Ira.
Because of your schedule?
Without Ira, it's a little bit difficult.
It's like the members don't know why. I don't like this feeling.
Ira, is today a scheduling conflict?
You're asking us? No one knows. It's like, "Why don't you share your schedule with the other members?
That's right. We always talk on LINE about going to Nami-Edison, and then we say how many days Amephra is off, but then there is also personal work.
No, I have many days off. I meet with people at Amefura.
No one can share.
I'm in trouble.
I want Amefla to send it out.I would like to see the Amefula company put it out there with a bang.
If I write it, no, there are others. If she writes it, well, there are others.
It's a tough schedule, isn't it? I wish I could go.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But I'll say that I haven't talked to candy in two weeks.
Why, we have a lot to talk about tonight, don't we? What do you have in mind?
But there's also the fact that the mini-album Coffee has been released.
And it's number one on the Oricon daily chart.
I am very happy.
Also, the music video for "Blow Your Mind," which was shot in Taiwan, has been released, and it has already received over 100,000 views, and now it has about 110,000 views.
And, what can I say?
I can't say enough, have you seen THE SECOND? I'm sure you've all seen it.
[Applause]
Gallup's victory was amazing, wasn't it?
I'm sorry. Yes, yes, but there's more to talk about, isn't there?
You're treating me as if I don't care about Mr. Gallup's victory?
I didn't say that.
It was great.
I think it's great that Gallup won.
But of course, it's more of a topic than us.
It's not really relevant.
The G7, this was a historic meeting.
Yes, the G7 is definitely in the news.
Can you say that? By the way, seven countries.
I could, but I thought I'd let Hana speak for herself.
I'll let only Hana have her own flower, so by all means, Hana-chan.
Thank you very much. But I can say it too, but I dare you. I dare you.
I'm going to tell Yuzu.
Today is Hana's turn.
You can prove you're smart.
There's a schedule that says, "Today is Hana's day.
It says today is Hana's day in the schedule.
That's not true. You can say so.
Yesterday you were very conspicuous, and today is also your turn to be conspicuous.
There are a lot of Hana people here.
I thought it would be strange for me to be too much of a show-off since there were so many Hua Pushers.
Cow was great.
Ken-kun was really great.
I can't say it, neither of us can say it.
I can't say anything about the G77 countries. Because I'm an idiot.
Please cut it out.
Because I'm an idiot. Only.
TikTok customers, please.
It's a real negative promotion.
That's not what I want to talk about, but I want to talk about one more thing,
You mean the Thank You Special for Oekan's 10,000 Instagram followers.
No, it's not. First of all.
Why the most calm.
We have a lot of other things to thank you for, such as archaic nation and so on.
Let's start with that.
Thank you for 10,000 people.
Oh, one more time next.
Why Coaster, why such a slow pace?
Have you heard about the mini-album coffee?
No, no, no. Please answer G7.
Why?
Then! America!
Yes, sir.
Can you do it?
Keitel Challenge!
Woo!
Can you write?
I don't know.
Seven, right?
But there's one that's a sure thing, right?
Just one?
Well, let's go return the positron.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's do it, Ichikawa-san.
Are you okay, Mr. Ichikawa?
I don't know.
You'll never know.
You never know. Run.
Ichikawa-san, pull over.
Why are you such a jerk?
I don't get it!
I don't know what to do.
You're going to rewrite it vertically?
I know seven countries.
Oh, my God.
G7.
I have no idea.
Three.
There's only three.
Two more.
I'm writing very smoothly.
In five panels.
Why don't you just write about the famous ones?
I don't think so.
I don't know. I have no idea.
How many did you just write?
Four.
That's fine. If you write something, something will happen.
I'm going to go.
Ready?
Oh!
Yes, I'm here.
Germany, Japan, USA, Brazil, South Korea, China, France, G7.
G7. This way. Did you know that? Gentlemen.
Yes, my G7 is here.
You already know it.Don't you already have.
The G7 is Japan, Germany, USA, Russia, France, UK, and China.
Yes, sir.
Let them all go down in flames somewhere.
What?
Yes, sir.
Well, what's the right answer?
Is there definitely a Russia or something?
Yes, sir.
Russia, right?
Russia is not so easy.
Do you have one in Germany?
No, we have one in Germany.
Because G, G, G.
There's Canada and Italy.
Oh, Canada!
That's for sure.
Oh, Italy.
Italy.
Italy, sure.
I don't know which one is different... what country is not close... no China... no this one... no this one... no this one...
I wrote that Russia is not likely and China is not likely, but I can't think of anything else.
I'm not a student, but this is a good place to start.
I don't have time for this, it's been 10 minutes.
We have a lot to talk about today, so can you please turn it off?
Erase, erase, erase.
It's a little awkward, isn't it? It's just like a pause.
How to moe when it's really annoying.
I say sound effects.
I'll definitely say tsun-tsun, the "moe" way.
I told you earlier... you weren't sure where to start, were you?
Thanks to all of you, we made it to number one on the Oricon Daily Chart.
I'm so happy that we got the number one spot on the Oricon Daily Chart last time, too.
I'd like to keep up the momentum and aim for the weekly ranking, but it's really thanks to all of you who have been coming to our Lily events and supporting us, so thank you very much.
I'm really grateful to all of you who have been coming to our release events and supporting us, so thank you very much.
How about you members?
I don't think it's a mini album at all... it's so gorgeous, I think.
I think my first guess right now is Tan Twister, and my second guess is Magic of Love.
Two new songs? I like "Flop Flop Morning" and "Magic of Love" a lot, too, but I don't know if I like them.
I like the live performance.
I think Tan Twister has the best live performance feel, and it changes a lot at each show.
I think the members are No. 1, and Magic of Love is No. 2.
I really like unison songs and songs sung by idols, but it's been a while since I've heard a unison song from Amehera.
We haven't had unison songs in a while. We haven't had unison songs at all, so when I heard this song for the first time in a long time, I thought it was really cute.
I'm torn.
I'm saying a different song every time I say this.
I'm saying a different song every time... but today... there's no "today"...
I'm saying "Flap Flap Morning" and "Magic of Love" today.
Why? I'm in a really cute mood today.
I'm really annoyed with Koji today, to say the least, and I really don't like it, so I'm going to say it now.
I've been with Hana since about an hour before the show started, and she's really annoying me.
I came early.
I'm really annoyed, and as soon as I enter, I'm always annoyed by Moka and Aira.
Moeka and Aira are always annoying, but the two of them...
We decided at Ameshabe that we'd only ask them three times if they liked their makeup this way or that way.
Despite that...
I really don't like this feeling, but she still asks me 10 times a day.
And as usual, I answered while thinking how annoying it was.
I think they're both cute, but Kojima today, he doesn't usually say such things.
I don't know what she meant. She said this eyeshadow isn't cute.
She suddenly said something like that?
I thought Kojima was a little strange today.
But when I said she was more beautiful than pretty, she started saying, "Am I pretty? She started saying, "Am I beautiful?
I was a little scared.
So I decided to be that type of person today.
And then she started saying I'm pretty today, too, and she was really excited about it.
And when she came into the room, she just walked in... and then she realized she was cute and left again.
That's how she started coming in.
She said, "You're so cute!" and started going in like that.
Suddenly she was like, "Yoo-hoo!
Can I ask you to play the role of a young lady?
No, no, no, I was going for that kind of character today.
I really thought I'd do it today.
I see.
I did the whole coming in and going out thing.
I just went with the normal routine.
Good night.
You're really going for it. Isn't it dangerous?
The most embarrassing part of this is that I get all dressed up until I sit down in the chair, and when I sit down in the chair, I fall.
This is the lamest part.
And yet, he strikes a very determined pose and stumbles.
I'm like, "Hey, don't say that.
I hate it so much.
That's why we have that song today.
So I was in that kind of mood. So I was in that kind of mood, so I chose "Flap Flap Morning.
I don't usually choose songs like that.
Magic of Love or some cute girl.
Oh, I see. That was a pain in the ass.
Is something wrong?
I was going to go as a popular girl today.
What do you mean?
I'm a very popular girl.
I'm popular today, aren't I?
Like, "I'm a popular girl today.
Something like that.
And the yuzu has descended.
Oh, my God.
I'm not supposed to be there today.
I'm not supposed to have that corner today.I will not have that corner today.
I just came from Dubai.
I don't have any plans.
I've just arrived from Dubai.
During the usual phone call with Kojima's parents.
Oh, hello. What's up? Dinner?
Oh, okay.
Bye-bye.
It's always like that.
All the time.
Today, he started calling Momoa.
I wondered what it was about.
I had Pad Thai at Ebisu for lunch today.
It was delicious.
Today's outfit?
I wore something really cute.
Okay. Bye bye.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
It's normal.
It's not like that at all.
You scared me. Let's talk about today.
I'm feeling a little better today.
Why?
Aren't you afraid?
You're not the same person, are you?
I feel good today.
Because you're Ira.
You look like Ira. I feel like this.
I feel good today.
I don't like it.
I got a lot of compliments yesterday.
No, it's not that.
To be honest.
A little more this way.
You should come a little more.
To be honest, I'm not on a diet today.
How does that make you feel?
I think the food's coming out.
I don't care what you're talking about.
That's why I had a flapjack morning.
I thought it would be nice. Thank you very much.
I'll be leaving now.
Thank you very much.
Please don't come back.
You're scaring me so much.
That's enough. This is the last one.
I bet you're glad you didn't write today.
You got a lot of buzz.
You look like a good girl who's ready to do whatever it is she has to do.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I could have been watching you all the time at Arthur's or something.
I'm scared.
I wonder if they were watching.
That's why the flap morning.
You made me sound like a very self-conscious woman.
That's why I'm going to choose two self-conscious songs today.
Not self-conscious songs.
This one is a little different.
But I can be a confident girl.
A confident girl.
Like Magic of Love.
That kind of tryker.
From the lyrics.
Look at me. I love you so much.
I'm a little confident.
Confident girl.
Magic of Love and.
I chose a lovely flapjack morning.
Today's ceremony.
This is Mayaka-chan.
Where's Moayaka?
I've always been the same, but I've been listening to
I often listen to "Fluttering Morning" and "One More Time".
I listen to a lot of music on the train,
Those two songs.
I listen to Batata Morning, One More Time, and Magic of Love in that order.
I listen to them in order. The songs I like.
Maybe it's not so much the songs I like, but the songs I sing.
No, it's not! No, it's not like that.
One More Time is my favorite.
And my next favorite song.
Do the songs you chose sound like "moe-kake" songs?
No, not at all.
What else do you like?
Eh?
Well, I like Gradation.
It's different from what I thought.
It's a little different.
Brian Maid.
What's another song?
What's the image of another song?
Like a lucky number.
Oh yeah, lucky number... listen again.
Yes.
What do you want me to say?
That's what it's like. I listen to those three songs
I listen to those three songs on a loop.
They're cute.
They're stylish and nice.Nice stylish song.
Just a nice super chat?
Yes, it is.
Mr. Coffey, I will continue to support you in other places because I am too busy to go to live shows.
Glad to hear it. Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
But maybe they would rather see us live than like this.
I think that's true.
It's great that 500 people came to see us today.
Wow, I'm so happy. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I have to go in.
But isn't it great?
Yes, it is.
I remember how much I used to remember you and me.
I'm the type of person who never forgets things like this,
There was a time when Amishabe had a really bad view count when Aira was not around.
I got pretty sick.
I wondered if it would be like this without the center, but more than 500 people watched the show even without the center.
I am happy.
If the center were here...
Please don't say that.
If you say that, I'll fall even more.
Oh, I see. It's great, isn't it?
Wonderful. Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
I hope you will listen to the coffee.
There are songs to suit all kinds of moods.
Songs to listen to when you need a pick-me-up, for example.
Do you want to give a little commentary on the songs, like, "You should listen to this when you feel like this..."?
But you said you like One More Time when it's hot,
It's been hot lately, so I like One More Time because it makes me feel cooler when I listen to it.
I recommend it. Outside.
Certainly.
For sure. I don't know how to put it. It's more like a pleasant coolness than an invigorating feeling.
It's like a breeze is blowing in your face.
I know what you mean. Like the ocean.
It's the kind of music that goes well with the ocean.
Yes, it is.
It's a reflection.
I get it.
Which song is Magic of Love for you, Hana?
From Hana's point of view, it makes me feel really good when I listen to it while I'm walking from my house to the nearest place.
There's no reason, right?
No, no, no. It's true. When I listen to Magic of Love, I'm the kind of person who sings while walking.
I'm the kind of person who sings along while thinking it's okay if there are other people around me.
It's amazing.
But I get really excited when I sing as if I'm an idol.
But I don't know what it is, and it's not the best, but it's not like I'm going to see my boyfriend or girlfriend,
But if I listen to it before going to see my idol or someone I like, it really lifts my spirits,
It makes me feel like I can be more cute.
Not only when I'm in love, but also when I meet a girl I like.
When I listen to "Magic of Love" or "Batata Batata Morning" when I want to raise my self-esteem, it really raises my spirits.
So when I listen to Batata Butterfly Morning while I'm putting on my makeup, it makes me feel like I'm more complete than usual.
Especially for girls, when they listen to these two songs, they think they are cute.
I feel like I can think they are cute. It gives me confidence.
When I do my makeup, it's true. They are perfect for that.
I recommend them to anyone who wants to feel pretty.
And the gradation is great for when you're feeling down.
It's amazing. I have to talk about it with the new songs, since there are so many new songs in a row.
You're asking about gradation all of a sudden.
Well, here we go.
Dance Sister is a time to challenge yourself, isn't it?
When you listen to it when you are going to challenge something, it makes you want to do your best and makes you feel a little lighter, doesn't it?
You can get into the mindset of "just give it a shot".
Also, when you want to improve your fluency.
Do you know any newscasters?
I recommend it.
It's definitely better.
Do newscasters watch this kind of American TV?
They might be watching it.
If you watch Amershabe, you're already getting on my nerves.
There's a newscaster in here.
They're probably on edge.
Is he here?
I think he's coming to Spacha. can the MC's please police the place somehow?
I feel incredibly uncomfortable watching this.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry might be good.
What about Bloyermind?
I recommend Bloyermind at night,
I like to listen to it in the bathtub,
I also listen to it in the bath.
It's a little bright, and I like to listen to it in the bathtub, where the image is calm and dark.
Or when I'm relaxing at home.
It would be good to listen to it when you are relaxing.
I guess so.
And this "Blowyer Mind",
The music video has been released, hasn't it?
Yes.
And the music video has been viewed more than 100,000 times!
It's now over 100,000 views!
Isn't it amazing that it has reached 110,000?
That's amazing.
I'm so happy.
It's 110,000.
I also got some comments from people who said they were recommended by TikTok and that they were really cool.
I'm very happy.I'm glad.
And aren't there more comments in English than usual?
Yes, I think so.
Maybe it's because Amefurashi has been getting a lot of attention in China, but...,
But there were also a lot of comments that were not from Japan.
It makes me happy.
I am happy.
We've never had 100,000 views in less than a few weeks before,
So we don't really feel it,
But I guess buzz is a powerful thing.
I wonder if we have already passed our lucky number.
I feel like we have already passed our lucky number.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The pace is totally different.
It's totally different.
I'm surprised.
It makes me happy.
Every time I wake up in the morning and see it.
I can't believe it.
It's amazing. I hope it will continue to grow.
Do you have any recommendations?
The music video.
I like that one. Yuzu is doing the "burn" thing.
I love it too. When I first saw it, I thought it was kind of cute.
I thought it was cute.
By the way, but aren't you doing the Yuzu Burn?
It looks a little bit like that.
And you're saying "burn". But Yuzu would never have done it.
Unless he didn't.
Because there isn't.
I thought he liked it when he said "bang" in some lyrics.
That's definitely not true. I'm doing it unconsciously.
You're not doing it? Really.
I definitely don't remember doing it.
I was so sleepy I forgot.
Isn't it the rap part?
It's before the third chorus.
I think it's the part where Ira sings before the third chorus.
It was cute.
I remember doing waves like this.
Wave was cute. I liked the wave.
Here it comes.
I'm full.
It was cute. Here it is.
Yuzu and not yuzu, Moehana and Hana were the recommended points.
Yuzu-chan beauties are cute this time.
Hey, don't say that this time. Don't say that this time.
I've been told "this time".
I like beautiful women this time too, especially Hana.
Ponytails are rare.
I think it's cute because it's rare.
Here?
Like 1:45 or 1:44.
There are people who became fans after watching the drama.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I don't remember doing it, so they probably cut out some parts and made it look good.
Isn't it so cute? He's doing the "bang" thing.
I've recently become a fan.
I recently became a fan.
Thanks for the fan. I'm glad.
I'm glad. Come and visit us, come and visit us live.
I'd love to see you.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad that those people are watching you speak.
I like that part about the barn.
You got it?
Sure did.
This bar.
It's so cute!
It's so cute.
It's so cute here.
Thank you.
I love raiding.
Really? I'm glad. Thank you.
And, you know, on a personal note,
When Moeka does the finger-pounding,
When she did that,
There is a shrine in Taiwan,
The shrine was a daytime shrine,
temple to the temple at night.
There is a scene where Moeka changes the shrine from a daytime shrine to a nighttime temple.
I love that part,
There was a piece of clothing here, wasn't there?
Was there a kimono?
A kimono.
It's too much.
Isn't it called a penny suit?
You might say "ichibun" or "ichibun-kit.
I have a penny suit.
This is, you know, this finger-patching,
Originally, Moeka was going to do it.
Like Mr. Suzuki's finger patting.
Even at the meeting, I said, "Moka, you're going to do it,
I'm going to do it like this.
But when it came time to go to Taiwan for the actual shooting,
I knew it,
I decided to use Airou for the finger patches.I was like, "I'm going to name her Airi-chan.
I'm going to name her Airi-chan.
What's that? Maybe I lost in the audition for the finger.
I lost the audition for the beautiful finger girl.
That's Airan, long and slender and beautiful.
She has beautifully shaped nails.
Even the shape of her nails is not good.
I lost the audition.
Surely, it's simple,
Moeka plays the guitar, so her nails are short,
It's a bit childish, isn't it?
She can't make her nails long.
That's why she didn't make it.
I did wonder if it was Aira.
She's beautiful.
But in the end, it ended up being Ms. Suzuki.
Oh!
Back!
Why did you go back to Moeka?
I don't know.
Did you look unhappy?
No, I didn't.
I think that's the word Suzuki-san got sulky.
I think it's my part.
So I'll do it.
Around 1 minute and 32 seconds.
But it was really hard work. I had to coordinate with the cameraman.
From here, day turns to night.
This is just a moment.
I had to adjust the position of the camera.
Where should we do it?
Twice, once in the morning and once at night.
It's so cool, isn't it?
It's hard to do it like that.
Dendenchi.
It was hard.
I love it here.
I was addicted to the end!
If you are going to Nagoya and Youth one-man shows
Thank you so much!
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm so happy.
What else?
Do you have any recommendations?
I think Yuzu should stay at Ilan.
This place is nice, isn't it?
Is there anything in particular?
Here.
I like that scene in Ilan.
Which one is it with?
Please play it after this.
Yes, ma'am.
Can I?
This place really looks like a real magazine.
It's like a professional magazine model. I like it a lot.
It was a little short, though.
Why are you crying?
One minute.
What is it?
What is it? No?
It wasn't about what Yuko showed him.
Huh?
Can she say something?
I'm sorry.
But the first flower is the very first one, right?
Right there.
Oh? Was it just after this?
Yes, after this.
Let's start from here.
I'm going to play it.
I wonder if there's music.
It's like a scene.
It was short, wasn't it?
When you play it like this, it's like, "Oh, no, it's too short.
Then it's really short.
This flower, impression flower is there too.
It's pretty, isn't it?
The color of this flower is really pretty.
It's used for something...
Ah, yes.
I quite like what they're doing with the flowers on the platform.
On a station platform.
You can't take pictures like that in Japan.
You have to go overseas, like Taiwan.
I saw a photo of flowers before,
It wasn't used here,
I was taking a picture of Hana before, but it wasn't used here,
I wanted them to use it,
I wanted them to use it.
Tell them to use it.
I can use it.
It's good, too, with power.
Sure.
Why does it have to be so awkward?
We don't have any Taiwanese stories.
But you stayed overnight in Taiwan, didn't you?
I thought you meant overnight.
You went there on a day trip, right?
You had this reaction after a one-day trip.
It might have been a day trip.It could have been a day trip.
The first day trip idea was.
Yes, that's right. Day trip schedule.
I asked if we could go on a day trip.
Just in time.
I thought we might have a shot at it.
How many hours would it take to get to Taiwan?
But surely it would be like leaving at midnight and returning in the morning?
About three hours, right?
It's not impossible.
With an LCC, it would be like leaving at midnight.
And you arrive at 3:00 or 4:00 am.
I see.
Well, we stayed overnight. We stayed overnight.
Well, we were staying overnight.
That was good.
We all checked in at the hotel, and while we were unpacking, I got a LINE from Yuka Moya, and it was a group LINE,
I got a LINE from Momoyuka, and it was a group LINE.
That's very rare, isn't it? It's so rare to get a group LINE from a person like that.
I've never received a group LINE from Sakao-chan, but I've never received a group LINE from Mayuka.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's almost never.
It's a group line of four people, just the members.
I was wondering what was going on, so I looked at it,
I wondered what it was about, and then I saw that it was from Yayuka. I wondered what was going on. I thought, "What does that mean?
I replied, "No, I have a bath," to which he replied, "I don't have a bath," to which I replied, "I don't have a bath,
I replied, "No, I have a bath," and he said, "I don't have a bath," and then he said, "What should I do? What should I do?
I couldn't do anything about it, so I came over here and said, "I don't know.
I couldn't do anything about it, so I came over here.
What's wrong? Oh, I don't know.
I went into the room, and I was worried about swelling and so on, so I decided to take a bath,
I wanted to take a bath, but when I entered the room, there was only a shower,
There was no bathtub.
I see. There was no bathtub.
That's right. There was no bathtub. I thought everyone else would have one, so I thought I would take a bath,
I thought everyone else would have one, so I thought I would take a bath, and when I called them on the phone, they told me that everyone else had one,
At that moment, I was very depressed.
Why?
Why? I was like, "Why?
Why didn't they give me a bathtub?
No, no, no. No, no, no, not to someone else,
Did you fall so far that you don't even have a bathtub?
Yes, that's right.
I thought, if it was a line, it would be an edge-cart wrinkle,
It's a lie.
I didn't think so,
What's Shin-chan's line, too?
It's true.
You're choosing this place?
Shin-chan is the worst.
It's true.
Which way should I hold it with my hair? It's a special treatment.
In a way.
You think you can say it any way you want.
So what happened?
I called the manager,
"Do you have it in your room? I said, "Yes,
She said yes,
So, things have changed a little bit.
Wow!
Wow.
Is that Matsuoka-san?
Ma-chan.
It's Ma-chan.
The talent didn't have a bathtub,
I couldn't allow the manager to have a bathtub.
Shut up.
He said it's unforgivable.
It's unforgivable.
I'm leaving.
Why?
I don't have a room.
You can't take it away.
Please leave now.
That's for sure.
That's a lie.
Tell him I'm sorry,
It was right after I got my luggage,
I was able to get in safely after being switched.
I was able to shoot a cute music video without any stains.
Yes, that's right.
We've been having trouble lately.
We are overseas, aren't we?
I think it's the south of the country.
Didn't Kristan make a lot of noise this morning?
Yes.
I had to wake up very early or very late.
I had to get up.
It was like getting up in the middle of the night, wasn't it?
Yes.
And I thought I couldn't take a bath at night anymore.
I thought, "I'll get up in the morning and take a bath.
It was no use.
Once more, I went to bed. I went to bed and couldn't stand up.
I had to stay up until midnight the night before, and then get up a little earlier to get ready for the next day's shoot.
I couldn't do it anymore. I was going to go in in the morning,I can't do it anymore. I was going to go in in the morning,
I heard the alarm this morning, but I couldn't get up at all,
I woke up a few minutes later than I had planned.
I was in a hurry to take a bath even though it was early.
I have long hair,
I have long hair, so a single shampoo rinse that you can buy on the market is not enough for me.
I thought the hotel would have it.
But I thought it would be provided at the hotel, so I brought only one shampoo.
It was used up.
And I thought that if I added more of the shampoo that came with the hotel, I would have enough.
So I decided to bring a good one that I liked and bulk it up.
And the shampoo.
So you were a little stingy?
Yes. I was stingy.
It was a hassle, and I didn't want to bring it.
So I did the shampoo and said OK.
Then we decided to do the rinse,
I looked at the right side of the page and saw something about a shampoo body.
It only said something about a shampoo body,
What? No conditioner?
There were only two kinds?
Yes. But the day before, I was wearing a cape and waxing very hard,
The other one, which I used only once, didn't come off at all, and it was all crispy.
I was in trouble.
But I had to leave the room in 30 minutes.
What was I going to do?
I called everyone.
You called everyone?
I called everyone, but they didn't answer, so I called them.
Then I looked around and thought there might be a front desk.
I called the front desk,
Excuse me, shampoo next, conditioner OK?
Wait a minute, what do you mean?
OK, OK, OK.
That's the order of things, isn't it?
OK, OK, OK, OK.
So, something like, you know, house, conditioner.
It's a room.
It's a house.
They were saying, "OK, OK.
Like, "I'll take it with me.
I got through to them.
And they understood, and they said "Haum tenkyu.
"Haum tenkyu.
I thought, "Thank God, I won't be late.
And then, "Here it is," he said, "Here it is.
Like, "Ja ja jaan.
Taiwanese people never say "jajaan.
They don't say that.
Not in Japan.
Not even in Japan.
"Ta-da-da-da-da.
They say.
I thought, "Ten-queue," and then I looked at it and saw that it was Cokey soap.
I wondered if this was conditioner.
I said "conditioner" and they said it was some kind of NO soap.
It's definitely a tenqueue.
I don't say soap.
I don't say NO NO soap.
NO NO conditioner. Shampoo, nex, conditioner. Shiny.
Absolutely shiny.
I don't have any more. I had to hurry, so I went into the room and she explained everything to me.
I had to hurry, so I went into the room and he explained everything to me, and he said, "This is for your body, and this is for your shampoo.
I said, "No, no, no, NO conditioner.
So I kicked him out of the room.
So I had to kick him out of the room.
I didn't have much time, so I had to go back to my room.
So I went over to Ms. Kainu's place and boom, boom, boom.
Mr. Yameli.
Mr. Yameli, right?
Yes, yes.
Do you have any conditioner? I said, "Yes, I have some conditioner," and he gave it to me.
So next time, I'll bring more.
Yes, I will.
It was a tough morning.
Well, well... If you shoot music videos overseas, you have a lot of things to do, don't you?
There are a lot of things.
But, you know, when we were about to crank it up, we had tapioca and stuff like that.
The food was delicious.
They gave me chicken.
The tapioca was really good.
Tapioca is so good, isn't it?
It's so good.
There is a difference between tapioca and the real tapioca.
It has cocoa tapioca in it, so it's really good.
The elasticity.
The tapioca itself is really delicious.
The taste is also delicious. And the drink.
It's just right.
I wonder what it is.
It's so delicious.
Just right.
I was happy.
We've all heard the episodes from the shoot.
But yuzu, dinner.
I'm talking about dinner.
It was during the shooting.It was during a photo shoot.
We came to dinner, to the location of the shoot.
You mean catering?
I don't know what you call catering.
They came.
And there was a huge line of food at the location of the shoot.
Bento?
Oh, bento.
What do you mean?
Bento, right?
How did you do that?
I don't know.
It's not that bad, is it?
I know what you mean.
Take whatever you want.
Is there that many?
Yeah, there's more and more and more kinds, and there are lunches and things like that.
Is that possible?
Don't you take a lot of breaks? And then you don't often eat in the office and shoot again?
In the case of Hohkahoka...
I'd like to take a break and eat it right then and there.
And then we'd eat on the spot.
We're all working together.
Because we don't always do that.
I'm always doing waki-waki-waki-waki-waki-waki-waki-waki-wa.
I have an image of going home and eating after everything is done.
I have an image of going home and eating.
I have the image of having a desk right there, and putting all the food on the table.
And then we eat in a relaxed atmosphere.
It was like a proper lunch time.
That's what I do, too.
We often eat outside.
I don't know if I'll ever eat there.
But it was delicious.
Udon rice... a good way to eat.
It was really good.
What was the best?
Well, I don't know... like the fried chicken.
I'm not talking about what was good.
That beef was good.
The beef was good.
The basket pastry was good, too.
The basket was delicious!
When you two get back...
Yes.
When we go, it's totally different from when we leave.
When I go, it's like... It's like...
One passport.
How much has it changed?
They double-checked me.
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm? They're gonna give me a "hmm?
Okay. - Okay.
I'll do it with my divine hands.
I'll do it with God's hands.
It's there, isn't it?
Not at all.
Not so much.
But when I was shooting...
I'm coming down from the elevator.
coming down from the elevator.
In my first music video.
I was in an elevator.
When we were filming, the moment it closed
I was told to press the open button and come out.
And when it closed...
I went upstairs.
It was a normal time of day
That's when the public was using it.
I went upstairs.
And the moment it opened...
I had to go back down.
So I went straight down.
In that wacky outfit.
I had to go upstairs.
It wasn't my own clothes.
It was so embarrassing.
The guy in the crazy outfit suddenly appeared in front of me.
I thought he was going to come out, but he came out.
He put a chair here and went downstairs.
Like an elevator guide or something.
It was like an elevator guide or something.
It was difficult.
So you entertained them with a lot of resistance.
Yeah, I did that a lot.
We shot it on a train platform.
Wasn't the music really stylish?
Station platform?
They play music in Japan, too.
Very much so.
Very stylish music.
The music was very stylish.
When the train was coming.
I don't know what kind of music it was.
I don't know.
TV
Music
It's so different from Japan.
It's beautiful.Beautiful.
It's like fashionable music.
Like, you can dance to it.
It was fun.
And what's more...
I was able to take a lot of pictures in places that you can't take pictures in Japan.
I was able to take a lot of pictures.
It's hard to take pictures of temples and such in Japan.
It's hard to take pictures of temples and such in Japan, isn't it?
We were able to get some really good shots.
It was so beautiful.
The way the light was shining so beautifully.
So I hope you guys will see a lot more of it.
I hope you guys will see a lot more of it.
If you haven't seen it yet
If you haven't seen it yet, please close this candy chat and go see it.
It looks good.
It's not about the show.
You don't have to see it.
It's for the next person who goes to Taiwan.
I don't want to tell the next person who goes to Taiwan...
I don't want to tell them about the cookies.
I got them for the bears.
Cookies.
I only bought one more.
Souvenir of the bears.
Cookies.
Tea and cocoa.
They're really good.
Amazing, right?
It's matcha.
Like matcha rice cakes.
With that chocolate.
Isn't it good?
It's like a matcha chocolate coating.
It was so good.
But I didn't buy another one.
What's with you?
She said she had a recommendation for a souvenir.
Yuzu, because I've bought it before.
It's delicious!
I didn't know it was a video.
I bought a yuzu and it was delicious.
You seem to like yuzu.
Why did you say that?
Because I was watching it from a different place.
She didn't ask.
She gave me a lot of stuff.
Ayala gave me this.
She gave me so much.
On the other hand, I bought...
Tea cookies.
I liked them so much I traded them.
Isn't that nice?
Yeah, they're good.
Tapioca
Pineapple Cake
A tapioca version of
It's so good!
Where is this?
Taipei
Airport
Where
Songshan
Airport
Souvenirs on the second floor of
Next to Starbucks
There was a Starbucks
There it is.
There's matcha green tea.
There's a bear one and a tapioca one.
It looks like it could be at either airport.
You're right, they're all everywhere.
It looks like it could be anywhere.
By all means, everyone.
Please buy one when you go to Taiwan.
The in-flight meal was delicious!
The food was great!
When we went to Thailand and Taiwan...
They served udon noodles, right?
I've never had udon before.
I went to Thailand and Taiwan.
I met udon for the first time
The first time I went to Thailand and Taiwan, I had a caviar attendant who came and served me
Spaghetti
or chicken
and she said something like
I went with spaghetti.
I opened it and out came udon noodles.
That's not spaghetti!
It was delicious.
Pasta.
Pasta?
Udon is not a word they use.
I guess people over there call it pasta.I guess people over there call it pasta.
Udon.
Udon is not a regular.
Or noodle.
That's right.
Very thick and sticky noodles
Seafood udon
Seafood pasta
When I opened it expecting pasta, I was surprised to see udon noodles.
When I opened it expecting pasta
Surprise!
But when I ate it, it was so sticky!
It was delicious!
But isn't the bread the best?
They definitely have bread.
No matter what you order.
It's really good!
Tutu Butter
Four kinds of tutu butter.
A few words from the shoot
I was really surprised.
The flight home
I don't know if it was the flight to or the flight back.
I was really...
I thought we were going to fall.
It was so...
It was so bumpy.
I don't know if it was the wind.
I don't know if it was the wind, but it was really shaking.
The three of you can't fly.
You know, you and me...
They were so scared.
Aira, right?
I asked him to look out the window next to me.
It was you.
The part where they landed.
What do you call that?
Yuzu.
It looks like a vista.
Don't tell Yuzu.
I really don't see it.
I couldn't see.
When I couldn't see the cassowary.
Mayuka kept asking me if I could see the cassowary.
It's falling.
But it's fine.
There's a city.
So we're running around here in the city.
Maybe she's really falling.
It doesn't look cool.
Don't tell me it's not.
Oh, no, no, no...
There's Internet.
It's there!
They were so scared.
It happens sometimes.
You get caught up in it.
I was scared on the way home.
I was scared.
I'm scared of the rocking.
I don't get yuzu-sick, so I'd rather go on a boat.
It's so much harder.
Does anyone else get drunk?
I don't know.
Next time I want to go by boat.
I don't like the time it takes.
We don't have to talk about boats.
I don't mind.
Then swim.
Okay. - Okay.
So, is there anything else?
But the food was good, wasn't it?
I'm so happy for you.
That's all.
I see.
What about that scene over there?
I heard it was difficult.
"I really put a lot of effort into that scene.
"Look at this part.
I see. That's what you mean.
Can you think of it as buzz-rhythm?
If you have something to say...
Next time you're here.
I'm here to talk.
You've got the acting thing, too, right?
That's right.
The three of them.
Hana was on the roof first.
And then at the end, the three of us found the flowers.
And then all four of us are on the rooftop.
There is a scene where the four of them perform together.
At first
Aira was looking for Hana by herself.
And then they meet up with each other.
At that time, they started thumping on the floor.
I was so surprised.
The first time I did it, I was terrible at it.
I didn't see it.
Moeimi was so bad at it.
Oh, Moeimi sucks at it.Oh, Moeimi is not very good at it.
Moehara just taps his head.
I had to act like I was going to do it.
I'm not very good at it.
Can I see that?
Oh, no.
Pikachu.
It doesn't fit in with the clown mind.
Please don't do this. Please don't do this.
Please don't stop.
Please don't ever stop.
It was a little difficult.
It's like having willpower.
I don't know.
You don't look like yourself in plain clothes.
I don't know how to do it.
It was difficult to act that way.
Isn't it hard to look back and be surprised?
It was difficult.
What was your family's reaction?
My family's reaction was great.
This time it was me and my sister.
She said it doesn't matter what we do.
Of course.
Everything is great!
This time, my sister, Mom and Hannah...
The three of us saw it together first.
We watched it together before it was released.
Our first impression was...
But Yuzu's visuals are really nice.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
What did you think?
You're a Moeka fan, aren't you, Hanamoto?
Yes, Hanae's a Moeka fan.
She always said Moeka was cute.
Moeka can't be. She's cute. I always said I didn't like her.
You're so sweet.
You're so sweet. I'm glad.
I'm glad.
How did it go? My mom...
But she always compliments me, like she always does.
She says it was good.
She says it's okay, that Moe is cute.
Your baby is cute.
I didn't say that.
Moe is the cutest.
You're making fun of me.
I'm making fun of you.
He always compliments me.
What about Yuzukake?
Yuzuketto and the others had a limited showing before the movie came out.
You saw it then.
I told my mom it was my music video and I wanted to see it.
She said she wanted to see it.
She said she wanted to see it, so I showed it to her, and she's been thinking about it for the past seven years.
I'm gonna spend the rest of my life thinking about how I showed it to you a day early.
It'll drag on forever, but it's okay.
But she still wants to see it.
Why don't you show it to him?
If I showed it to you...
If he sees it...
I was looking at it.
She started asking to see it again.
You sure? I said, "Well, I've been showing you that second one for 14 years.
And then the next day, he could watch it again.
It's gonna drag on for 14 years, but I still want to see it.
I told her I wanted to see it.
Mom's gonna want to see it so bad.
Send it to my mom.
You want her to see it the day it opens?
She's like, "I want to see it.
They were watching it the whole time it was on opening day.
I can hear something... coming from the bathroom or something.
Blower Mind.
It's on all the time when I call her.
Are you watching?
I can hear it.
I've yet to see a complete stranger on the train.
I've yet to see a complete stranger on the train watching a video of raindrops.
But you know how they're showing raindrops on TikTok these days?
When I sit down and catch a glimpse of someone watching TikTok, it makes me want to watch it.
I'm like, "I wonder if it's going to rain.
Don't your friends tell you that? They say it comes out a lot.
They say that a lot.
I mean, my mom said she's going to call me.
From my friends.
I've been getting a lot of calls from friends telling me that I'm getting a lot of buzz about the rain shower.
Isn't it amazing?
Like, "We're rooting for you, behind your back.
Behind my back.
But I have a friend whose mom lives in Yokohama.
She came out and said how great it was.
And I got to perform for a minute.
And I also performed at Kannon Elevy.
It's a TV program.
You can't see it in Yokohama or Tokyo.Yokohama, you can't see it in Tokyo.
You can't see them, so you have them follow you.
I couldn't see it, so I had to burn it all and bring it back.
And he watched everything.
And he sent my mom a LINE with all his impressions of the talk.
Isn't that sweet?
She's so sweet.
I've had friends tell me that it's because kids nowadays watch TikTok.
But it makes me happy to hear it from the current generation.
What would you do if you actually saw her on the train?
What should I do?
I'll just sit next to them.
Let's do it like this.
I'm very appealing.
I'd do it like this.
I'm gonna do it like this.
I'm gonna do some drama.
What if they say, "Oh, you're gonna do it?
I'd say, "Here I come.
I'd say, "Hey, come here.
I'd say, "Hey.
You're two minutes away.
Can you call out to them?
Will you call out to the group?
You're gonna have to call them yourself.
That's me.
If I was in the city, I would.
What do you mean?
I wouldn't do it if it was near my house.
If I was in the city, I would.
If it's a group of people you think they might talk to.
They'd ask.
I'll tell them it's me.
I might say, "By the way, this is me, so please support me.
I'd be tempted to say something like that.
I'd say, "Please like this.
I want to see it.
I want to taste it.
Maybe we'll be close.
I'm looking forward to it.
Keep up the good work, Blow Your Mind!
Thank you very much.
Well...
Thanks for practicing yesterday, Ayako.
Thank you so much for your hard work!
What a time!
How many times have I told you?
I was about to hang up.
Shin-chan started it
I even blamed others
I was going to hang up so many times
You're never on time anyway.
I was making good progress.
Maybe there's someone watching this.
But isn't it great?
Yeah, it is.
We're only at 540 right now.
So, I guess it's okay if it grows.
Thanks for practicing, Aya.
Thank you for your hard work.
Every year, every year
Thank you so much to everyone at Rinpoche Rinpoche Rinpoche Rinpoche Rinpoche Rinpoche Rinpoche
Thank you so much!
That's what we've been doing with the abstinence syndrome.
Isn't it great?
But you know what?
The first time...
You know what?
I had to ego this whole period.
The first time...
I got a lot of comments like.
I got a lot of comments like, "I hope you'll do well from now on.
This time, when we ego-tested them, they said, "Thank you for participating again this year, Ura-chan.
I think it's because of you that we were able to do what we did.
We are so happy that Arline showed us so many good things about her and we are so grateful to her.
We're so grateful that Aaryn showed us so many good things, and now we're getting words of thanks from Mr. Prilov.
We are so thankful that Arline showed us so many great things, and we are so thankful that Mr. Prilov thanked us for standing up for Arline.
Not a single person at Rainflash is for Arnie... no, that's because we're all for Arline... but...
But Arline's a fan of... what's with the love dollar... it comes with everything!
but to be honest...
I can't say that I've become a fan of the two of them.
So it's funny... you can say there's no one else who's a fan of Ernie and Arline... or you can say it like that... but I can't say I've become a fan of them.
It's a business.
But, you know, to be honest, I'm pretty much an Arline guy, so I'm pretty much leaning towards that.
I know... you know... you love it... every time... but... it's funny... it's like there's no one in this wave right now.
But I can't say because it's like it's funny that I don't have a favorite in this wave, but I've been in it for about five years now.
I've been following Arline for about five years now.
Aya Takanari
I think you and Rinrin are the best pair, but by the way, Kanako is my only idol.
I get the feeling she's not really into me.
I wonder what she'd say if she really wanted to.
The ideal idol... so personable... it's easy to see how she grew up to be so kind-hearted.
The way she does everything for us, the way she goes to bat for us... it makes me wish I could be her mentor.
This was the first time for the star-prize students to appear on the stage, and they were like juniors to us.
But we really wanted to be friends with them.
I wondered if there were others like us juniors.
She is so cute.
She came to the show?
But she also danced for us at the "flap flap mornings" and other events with the students of Starply,
They talked a lot.They talk a lot.
They talk a lot.
You guys talk first.
We met at the Lilly, didn't we?
You were working here, right? And so on,
They say you're cute.
You're cute.
They were so friendly.
He's so cute.
He was so cute. It was so cute when he said puns.
I don't want to say anything because it would be dangerous.
I shouldn't say anything.
I shouldn't say it, but he was talking about where he lives.
They were talking about where they live.
I don't think she would say such a weird thing with a star-prize student like that, do you?
They're both just candy floss.
They're not candy floss, you know.
So, there were cameras around her all the time,
There were cameras around the staply students all the time, so it was like a close-up,
But even though there were cameras around, the seniors should have taken that into consideration.
Even though he was a senior, he was very abstract.
It's the opposite of what I'm supposed to say.
Even though I have it.
If you cut the audio, it would never end.
Do you live there? There? What time are you going home today?
You're from here, aren't you?
It didn't work again.
Everything's not working.
Amefura hasn't come out once.
He's talking a lot.
It's all LG.
It's just that I can't use them without talking.
Waste of cuts. Waste of tape.
She's cute, isn't she?
We exchanged contact information.
What? We did something.
You did? I was so surprised.
You've been saying that for a while.
You're very aggressive. Lately.
Recently, you mean you're more interested in younger girls?
Yes, I do. I want to be cute with them.
I just want to be with them.
How about your contact information?
I have. I'm sorry about that,
Come back.
He's cute.
I want them to get really used to me. I don't know what to do.
But, you know, I'm the one,
I'll be like, "Of course I'm Aaryn...
I know how you feel, but you want me to get used to it.
I know how you feel, but I want you to be very familiar with me.
But I don't know what to do.
But I feel much more at ease now than I did the first time.
I felt like he was talking to me as if we were close to each other.
That's for sure. We can meet again at Yuzuki's room next time.
I want to see you again and again.
I want to get to know you better.
At the end, she said good-bye and told me to be careful.
He was so cute. He was so cute.
Super cute.
He was really cute.
Where did Arline go?
Aaryn always leaves a photo album and a message card in our dressing room every year,
There is one point here, isn't there?
One point.
A message card.
Oh, yes. Is this a wonderful thing?
I was writing to a group of people, and there was a story with a message or something,
I looked at it, and I submitted mine in the story,
I put it in the story, and it said, "Thank you so much again this year, Amefera-chan.
Do you know how great this is?
I don't know.
What? You don't get it now?
You mean seriously?
Yes!
Not really, but seriously?
Yes! Thank you so much.
I see.
We were just saying thank you so much to everyone this year.
We were.
So it was a comparison?
Yes, it was.
The Sequoia Group.
It's all there, you know.
It was on the table!
You mean all the rats?
Yes.
A dirty one.
Only ours said "for real".
Yay!
This power word "seriously".
Don't say it!
Do you know how destructive "seriously" is?
We use "seriously" too, so you know what I mean.
Seriously is really serious.
I don't know what to call it.
It's something you can use because you have a little bit of trust and can soften your words.
When we first started out, Aryn never said "thank you" in a serious way.
Thank you so much.Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Like, thank you for coming again this year.
But seriously, thank you this year.
Yay!
It's for real!
I got it from Arline.
Isn't it amazing?
I think this is going to be pretty great.
When we saw the message, we all thought.
That was the first thing that caught our attention.
We all fell in love with it.
Seriously!
I'm serious! I'm going to check out the scene.
Let's check out the scene.
Aaryn.
Just a coincidence.
I don't want you to dig too deep into that part.
When you end it on a dreamy note.
I'm just dreaming about my own fantasies,
I'd like it to end like this.
But maybe we were in the same dressing room as Harima and Rumpan.
That's why we only compared Harima and Rumpan.
No, I went to Terapo's dressing room too.
Oh, really?
So fast!
That's too much!
I said, "Excuse me for disturbing you,
I said, "Oh, I'm sorry to bother you.
No, no, no.
It's a lie.
I went to see Miyachan when I had something to do.
I wanted to see it, too.
Oh, you didn't?
Seriously, you didn't?
Oh!
Yum!
That's the worst.
You're really cute. It's so cute.
I'm really looking forward to the concept this year and every year,
This year was like a world of toys,
We performed as toys.
We performed as toys, but our costumes were totally different from each other.
It seems so.
It's the same every year,
But everyone wears these costumes for Amihura.
Everyone is different.
What about you, Hara-chan?
First, I was the red hero,
After that, I played as Ken-kun.
And Mayuka?
In an ethnic costume,
Then Barbie-chan in Barbie.
Red Barbie.
Liz is a stuffed cow at first,
And then Barbie's yellow one.
Barbie.
I was able to wear it.
I'm really happy.
And after that,
With the haytails,
After that is a white wappi with polka dots pink or purplish polka dots.
Like white pink and black.
She has a nice style.
A styled dress with a ponytail.
Yes.
Like, you can already tell.
But really,
After all, the enemy of this affair,
The caname of the show,
Barbie's block.
I think this is a very important part of the show.
Everything is important,
But that part is the most important,
There are many sudden developments.
That's the point,
Haneda City is a back-up dancer,
I am happy that Haneda City is on stage as a back-up dancer.
I am happy.
I'm really happy.
It's great.
Important positions are entrusted to you.
That's right.
And what's more, this time,
I'm going to play Barbie's partner,
a very important position,
Kojima Uchino!
Wow! You did it!
I wanted to do it so badly!
I'm really glad I'm doing this character.
I like long hair, but I'm glad I went with short hair.
You must have had about 10 cm heels in your shoes, right?
Arin had light blue heels in them that were about 10 centimeters or more.
I was wearing shoes with super high heels, Barbie.
At first they were just regular sneakers.
Too small for me. I was originally about the same height as Arin,
I thought it wouldn't look good if Ken-kun was shorter,
So I put high in-heels inside my boots and wore them as secret boots.
You wouldn't know it if you saw it normally, but I was dancing on my toes.
I put in 5 minutes, 4 or 5 minutes.I put it in for five minutes, four, five minutes.
I was putting in a lot of ba-ba-boom.
He was so tall, his wings.
She had a beautiful style.
But I was also entrusted to do the Amehura dance scene in the middle of the show,
I really want to thank Arin for letting me dance for quite a long time.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
But even after the event, I met Arin's mom.
When we passed each other, we were like, "Thanks for the candyfloss.
We had plans to go to Disney with Namiya Girls Arts Clear,
I'm going to go to Disney.
It's just right now, so we're making a lot of progress.
It's just the two of us now.
Normally, the juniors have to take care of things,
But the senior PVP has been very kind in making sure our plans are in order.
When are you going?
I'm still a little vague, and he said he wasn't sure yet.
I want to tell you as soon as possible.
Arin is really in charge.
She's already decided what day she'll come. She's already decided.
That's so nice of her.
Yes, that's right. So..,
Arin's mom asked if I could go with her. She wants to go to Disneyland.
So cute!
She said, "Please listen.
Please listen to me.
I'm not a straight man, am I?
Arin-mama was cute.
And she's so kind.
She said everyone's name: Ana-chan, Yuu-chan, and Maika-chan.
Did you get her to remember your name?
That's right. She's so kind.
And she also told me that Arin was always loving on Amihura at home.
Amihura is very dear to me at home.
I'm so happy.
Arin's mom is really too much of an angel.
It was a happy day, wasn't it?
Right up to the end.
You mean you're talking about going to Disney with that wave shop, right?
That's for sure.
So cute!
I wish I could go to that world line.
Arin told Mom about Yu and the others.
I'm so glad.
And I understand.
It's scary.
That's really sweet.
I was so happy.
It was an ayakan nation.
Please do it again.
It was cute. Arin.
I was so happy.
It was fun. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
So, 10 years have already passed,
There are many relevees where you can meet us.
Oh!
I would like to do this project that has become a tradition.
If you say a word at the benefit, we'll say something for you,
So this time, Ichikawa-san.
Yes, I'm Ichikawa-san.
What kind of benefit will I get if I say what I want to say?
I can't aim to write anymore, is that okay?
Yes.
Is that okay?
Let's see, here's the name.
If it's Yuzu...
Yuzu-chan cha-cha-cha, toy cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha.
Moe, Chachacha, Oke... Moe Kachacha, no.
Sometimes, I want you to tell me what you want to show me, or something like that.
Some people don't say that. You have to say it.
You have to say it.
Ai-chan's cha-cha-cha, Hana-chan's cha-cha-cha, Moe-chan's cha-cha-cha, Yu-kun's cha-cha-cha, please.
Yes, please.
Tell me?
Say?
What's in it?
Say this.
I'll say something like, "I love you" in the sound of the animal you want me to use as a diaper.
I see.
What are you gonna do? You have to say "okapi" or something.
I don't know.
I love you, peepee.
I'm definitely not a pea.
I'm sure there are people like that.
Well, when I say it like that, you'll just have to imagine it.
Like, an anteater.
Imagine that.
Oh, my God, what would happen if I said that?
I love you, Quie.
I love it.
I know you're in there.
Ladies and gentlemen, the benefit.
But it's a long one.
I'm counting on you.
Can you remember it?
Someone won't see you, so just say it.
What are you talking about?
Who is this guy?
Ai's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy!Ai's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy's daddy
Hmm?
What is it?
Please don't do this.
This is the guy downstairs.
I feel sorry for him.
I want you to do it.
I'd like to see it.
I don't want to tell anyone.
You don't want to tell him?
It's only natural.
Of course.
I don't know what to do.
We laughed so hard.
It ended awkwardly.
Gamoyama said...
What?
There were a lot of things...
Just tell me.
It's too much fun.
I'm sure you're aware of that.
Please, please, please.
Well, that's that.
I'd like to introduce to you
Prior to the release of our mini-album Coffee
We are currently holding the Lilyway to rave reviews.
I'd like to give you some details and announcements.
First of all, the releaseway I was talking about.
The earliest date is June 4.
It will be held at Raraport Tokugawa Tatehi.
The first part will be at 1:00 p.m. and the second part at 4:00 p.m.
Then on the 11th, we will be at the Aeon Mall Tsunemei.
Please come!
Next is the last day on the 24th.
We will be at Raraport Toyosu.
The time is a little bit low.
We're aiming to get 500 people to the show.
I hope we can get 500 people somewhere.
I think it's pretty easy to come to Toyosu.
Please come and join us!
Thank you very much.
And...
Oh, over here!
The first group of Namiya Girls will be holding a traveling performance "Kimi to Kimi again"!
The place is Sporty High East.
It will be held on May 28th.
The first part will start at 3:15 p.m. and the second part will start at 7:15 p.m.
Tickets are available until 23:59 today!
This will be our first live performance as a 7-member group!
Please come and join us!
We'll be waiting for you!
And then there's that...
I don't know.
I don't know if we'll do it.
I don't know if I'll do it, but if there are people who only do it once in a while
I don't know, maybe during the romance at Arsol.
I don't know.
We did it at Aasol.
I don't know, but there might be.
We've only played Romance in the Middle about 4 times.
If you would like to see us play this song at Namaya, please let us know.
I'd appreciate it if you could do it.
Amurashi will be appearing on the May 22nd and May 23rd RecoMain Pickup!
Thank you very much for all the e-mails and comments!
Radio.
Yes, it will be on the radio. The time is from 23:30 to 23:40.
Please listen to it!
Please do.
Well, that was fun.
And Blow Your Mind has been chosen as TBS Radio's song of the night recommendation!
I'm so happy!
So happy for you!
JUMP
Jump
Because a lot of people listen to it
I'm glad
It's from today to the 28th.
The time slot is from 25:00 to 27:00.
I hope you will all listen to it.
Please do.
Some of you radio heavy-distributors are here.
Okada-san, you called me Junk at first.
Please don't say that.
I thought it was junk.
But it's a U.
Which one is it? I didn't want to make a mistake.
I thought it was junk.
I thought, "There's no such thing as junk.
So I checked.
But you asked me if it was junk.
So I said, "Is it junk?
I said, "Junk" is fine.
But I thought, "Is it Junk?
I didn't want her to think I couldn't read "U".
I said "Junk", but I don't care about "junk".
I don't care about junk.
Please listen to me.
Negative promotion!
I'm going to be on Shake Up World tomorrow!I will be appearing on Shake Up World tomorrow!
I'm sorry, I didn't have my panda costume available last week.
Too bad, I wish I could have seen it.
But I'll be lame tomorrow.
Really?
I've been waiting for you.
So, tomorrow, I'll be wearing a panda costume and a panda hairstyle.
I'd like to play a panda game at the benefit.
If you win, I'll give you a signed solo check.
We are looking forward to seeing you at the party.
I've made friends with some of the girls there.
I'd be happy if you could come and play with us.
Please do!
I'm getting a lot of panda emojis.
Are they looking forward to it?
And I'll be performing at Yuzuki's Room Fest 2023!
I'm so glad.
This is Yuzuki-chan's Yuzuki's Room festival, which is a two-part event.
We will be performing in the second part tomorrow.
It's been a while since we've performed at Yuzuki's Room festival, so we're really looking forward to it, and we're also looking forward to seeing the Stop Law students.
I'm also looking forward to seeing the students of Stop Law again.
We're looking forward to seeing you all there!
I don't want them to get too close.
Why?
Mr. Tomiura says he loves you very much.
But you know, I only got to meet the high school students this time.
I hope I can meet everyone else.
Ayano is there too?
Yes, Enano-chan will be there too.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
I'll do my best
Please come if you want.
Please do.
Yes, I'm here.
Perfume probability 100% on May 25th
Happy Amekafe CookpadLIVE on May 25th
This time I'll be performing as a pair with Yuzumoyaka.
Anyone can watch it for free on the Cookpad app.
I'd be happy if you could take a look.
I'd appreciate it if you could take a look.
I wonder what we're going to make?
I'm looking forward to seeing what you make!
June 10 is open recording Vol. 2!
We're doing a radio show called "Amefura Night" on Thursdays from 24:30 to 25:00.
We are doing a radio show called "Amefura Night" on Thursdays from 24:30 to 25:00.
We will have the second open recording on June 10.
It will be held at a place called Kiwa in Tennoji on June 10.
The application period is until 23:59 on May 24.
It will be a fun public recording.
I hope you can come!
Please come!
And here it is!
One of the biggest circuit festival in Nagoya
on June 11.
We will be performing at this festival.
On June 11th, there will be Lily Bed here.
I hope you can come to both of them!
Please come!
And last but not least.
July 9th.
Tickets for Bio-Sai are now on sale!
It will be held at 2 in Shinjuku.
There are two parts to the event.
We are both aiming for a soulful outing!
Both the first part and the second part are available.
Both parts 1 and 2 are really different from each other.
I'm sure you'll have fun no matter which one you come to.
I'm sure you'll have a great time.
I would be very happy if you could come to the show with your friends and family.
Thank you very much.
We collaborated last year, didn't we?
Maybe...
That's right.
Yes, it is.
I've already said that.
I don't know why he's suddenly muddying the waters here.
You've said so many things in such a big way.
But we're pretty excited about this collaboration.
It's going to be an exciting collaboration.
So please look forward to it.
And there's a new song, too.
That's right.
An inside song.
A song for the inner circle.
There might be.
Maybe there is.
No, there might be
We're already selling it with that.
Can you not muddy the waters?
If it's not there, it's pretty bad.
By proxy.
Maybe...
There might be new songs.
By all means, everyone!
April 9th.
Please do!
So that's the end of the announcement?
Yes, sir.
Then, of course, we'll end with this corner.
I'll be back this week.I'll be back this week.
That's what I meant. Sorry, everyone.
It is time to say goodbye.
I'm going to stop now.
I have to use my phone,
I'm going to hang up.
I'm sorry, really.
I really don't like today's flowers.
What is it today?
I think I'm going to say goodbye to you as soon as the play is over.
What's today?
I'm going to sleep.
I think we'll just say bye-bye.
I don't think so.
I wonder if Suik is working today.
Today she's moving.
He must be moving a lot.
He is shouting and moving, isn't he?
Yes, they are moving a lot.
This week's suikku is Law from One Piece, which I love.
I took this picture of me.
I took a picture of that Suik.
I saw it anyway, so it's okay.
I didn't see anything, but that's okay.
You didn't see it?
But it's okay.
Here we go.
It's not moving.
It's moving, Han.
You're moving.
Thank you very much.
It's cute, but it's not moving.
Yes, what do you mean?
It was Osumi again this week.
Thank you very much.
Very nice project.
Well, that's why it's time to say goodbye.
I wish everyone a good luck for the week ahead.
We will say goodbye with a corner of Moe Moe Magic, a spell to do your best from Moeko.
Today is a first-class full day, which is supposed to be a good day to start something,
I love chocolate, and I eat quite a bit of it every day.
So starting today, I'll have no more than five pieces of chocolate a day, and no more than five grains.
But you know how Moeko eats 3 bags of chocolate a day?
I seriously can't stop.
Is that okay? Starting today. You're sure you're okay with it?
It's a good time to eat.
It's good, isn't it?
It's a good thing to start today.
Good luck.
Please report to us every time you eat chocolate.
I ate this. Just chocolate is fine.
If there is something that you eat too much of, please let us know,
I think it will be a good thing if you start by deciding to eat less than five pieces from today onward.
That's all.
Is it a spell?
Yes, it is. This is a spell.
I have a wide range.
I see. A wide variety.
Where do you come from, by the way?
I'm quite something.
I'm pretty thick.
You seem to be thick.
Like this.
Like this, like this, like this, like this.
Thank you very much. Again.
No, no, no. From afar.
It's quite far.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Please go home.
Let's all go together for the last time.
Seino.
Ameya de ri chumoame hurachameri.
Ame-chame for short.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.